■
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯：賽太公  小米山藥  跌跌不愛吃青椒  醉芝士
校對：法蘭克YY貓  大香腸賽太公 總監   YY貓
后期：加森     時間軸：YY貓
好漢兩個半
第十一季  第九集
我通常都沒機會在科技展上認識
I don't usually meet women as beautiful as you
你這么漂亮的美女
at a tech convention.
你嘴真甜
Aw, that's very sweet.
你也是會上最帥的帥哥
And you were definitely the hottest guy there.
謝謝  雖然說
Thank you. Although, to be fair,
當科技展上最帥的男的感覺...
being the hottest guy at a tech convention is kind of like...
就像是在科技展上當最帥的男的...
well, being the hottest guy at a tech convention.
不過有一次我看到賈斯丁·汀布萊克[男星]
Although, once, I saw Justin Timberlake
出席微軟的派對呢
at a Microsoft party.
一泡一個準
Lady boner!
他的確是為微軟8系統帶來了性感元素
Yes, he did bring sexy back to Windows 8.
你說你是在谷歌工作嗎
So, you said you work for Google?
是的  在模特[建模]部門
That's right, in the modeling department.
很不錯啊  是例如圖像渲染
Oh, that's awesome. Like graphic rendering
與3D制圖嗎
and 3-D imaging?
更像是在指手畫腳啦
More like pointing.
"谷歌全新推出
"New from Google,
理解無能的科技玩意"
confusing tech crap."
所以你是真模特
Oh, so you're, like, a model-model?
谷歌谷歌  "鼓"起來高歌
Yep. You can't spell Google without "Ogle."
對吧
Can you?
不對
No, you can't.
但其實我并不想在科技展上當模特
But being a model at tech shows isn't what I really want to do.
只是為了賺錢糊口而已
I just do it to pay the bills.
我懂  那你的終極夢想是什么
Oh, I get it. What's your ultimate goal?
我希望能教人們識字
I want to help teach people to read.
好高尚的夢想  你想當老師啊
Oh, that's noble. So, you want to be a teacher.
我想當下一個字謎游戲的傳奇女主持
No, I want to be the next Vanna White.
你是認真的啊
Oh, you're serious.
對啊  你看她有一份好工作
Yeah. I mean, she has an amazing job,
總是穿得超漂亮  發型也超漂亮
she wears amazing outfits and she has amazing hair.
某人也超需要學個新形容詞啊
Somebody needs to buy a new, amazing adjective.
你不能買形容詞
You can't buy adjectives.
你只能買母音[節目游戲規則]
You can only buy vowels.
好的
Right.
只能賣母音
Only vowels.
我還欠你一杯飲料
Well, I owe you another drink.
O  K[猜字]
"O." "K."
今晚不會有I[我]進入U[你]的事情發生了
Certainly won't be any "I" in "U" Tonight.
那個妞真是美呆了
Wow, that girl is gorgeous.
她是個模特兒
Yeah, she's a model.
我們之間不來電
We don't really have a connection.
她腦子不太好
She's not very bright.
我覺得她會認為矽谷是一個
I think she thinks Silicon Valley is the place
女人去做矽膠假奶的地方
where women go to get a boob job.
你想要有智力上的刺激啊
Oh, you want intellectual stimulation.
那你何不一邊看著科研節目
Uh, why don't you watch an episode of Nova
一邊操翻她呢
while you're banging her brains out?
我要去跟她說我們不來電了
No, I'm gonna go tell her it's not gonna work out.
你不想上她  能讓給我嗎
Well, if you don't want her, can I have her?
行啊  我們互換衣服  她一定"認不出"
Oh, sure, let's change shirts. Maybe she won't notice.
她真笨成這樣啊
Oh, she's that dumb?
太好了
Great.
沃頓
Walden!
有海鷗...
Look, a seagu...
天啊
Oh, my God.
等等
Wait.
我們還沒互換衣服呢
We didn't switch shirts yet.
在干嘛呢
Hey, what's going on?
剛才在清理我的衣櫥
I was cleaning out my closet
發現了一箱杰克的舊東西
and I found a box of Jake's old stuff.
那挺好啊
Aw, that's sweet.
誰是杰克啊
Who's Jake?
我兒子  你堂弟
My son. Y-Your cousin.
對哦
Oh, right.
他是怎么死的
Oh, and how did he die?
他沒死呢  他參軍去了
Oh, no, h-he's not dead. He's in the Army.
好煙斗
Ah. Nice bong.
想必他打的不是抗毒的戰爭
Guess he's not fighting the war on drugs.
那是蜂鳥喂食器
No, that-that is a hummingbird feeder.
他在美術課上做的
He made it in art class.
手工藝課上  我也做了一個火車笛
And in shop class, I made a train whistle.
嗚嗚[大麻  大麻]
Weed, weed!
我不是開玩笑
No, no, seriously.
在他讀高中時的有一年暑假
Uh, one summer, back in high school,
他跟他朋友喜歡上了賞鳥
he and his friends got into bird watching.
他們會一整天都在森林里混...
They'd spend all day out in the woods, and they'd...
笑開懷地回家
they'd come back laughing and...
天啊  我真是個傻逼
Oh, God, I'm an idiot.
別擔心  所有家長都是傻逼
Don't worry. All parents are idiots.
我媽以前也以為我只是被反鎖在浴室里
My mom used to think I was locked in the bathroom all day
然后里面有只電動牙刷
with an electric toothbrush.
我第一任妻子也總是在用她的電動牙...
My first wife was always using her electric tooth...
天啊  我是超級大傻逼
God, I am an idiot.
你看  他以前的成績單
Oh, look at this. One of his old report cards.
還看得到他想偷換成績的印子
Oh, you can still see where he tried to change his grades.
他把所有的C
Yeah, he changed the C's.
都換成了D
To D's.
不過那年接他的校車的確換成接智障的小校車
Yeah. That was the year his bus got a little shorter.
不過  也不是那么壞
But, you know, in his defense,
他的老師那年也有變化
his teacher changed that year, too.
也從C變成了D[罩杯]
She went from C's to D's.
你晚上都是干這種無聊事度過的嗎
Is this how you're spending your night?
不不  等會我還打算刮背毛
Oh, no, no. Later, I'm going to shave my back.
如果你不忙的話...
Oh, actually, if you're not busy...
我忙  你也得忙
I am. And so are you.
我要去喝酒  沃頓呢
I'm gonna get a drink. Where's Walden?
他得把他的女伴送去醫院
Oh, he had to take his date to the hospital.
有東西卡在她身體里的哪個洞里了嗎
Ooh, what are they pulling out, and from where?
不是你想的那樣
No, it-it's nothing like that.
她當時在看天空  然后摔下了陽臺
She was looking up at the sky and she fell off the deck.
-嗑藥了嗎  -沒有
- High? - No.
-喝醉了嗎  -沒有
- Drunk? - No.
-模特嗎  -是的
- Model? - Yeah.
你還好嗎
How you feeling?
我沒事
I'm all right.
我們得填一下這個表
Uh, well, we need to fill out this paperwork.
名字是  納丁
So, uh, first name, Nadine.
這有點尷尬  我不知道你的姓
This is awkward. I don't know your last name.
是H  O  R  E
It's H-O-R-E.
H  O  R  E
H-o-r-e.
音似胡兒[歡呼]嗎
Like "Hooray"?
不  音似霍爾[妓女]
No, like "Whore."
你覺得我該改嗎
You think I should change it?
不  你該自豪
No, be proud.
這名字可是從你祖上流傳下來的  霍爾
I'm sure you come from a long line of... Hores.
你這里有親戚嗎
Uh, any relatives I can call?
沒有  他們都在東邊
No, they're all back east.
洛杉磯只有我一個霍爾[妓女]
I'm the only Hore in Los Angeles.
我還是保留意見吧
Agree to disagree.
緊急情況聯系人  沒有家人的話
Emergency contacts. Okay, so no family.
那你有朋友嗎  室友呢
Uh, friends? Roommates?
除了初次約會對象  有其他熟人嗎
Anyone you've gone on more than one date with?
沒有
Not really.
我一個人住
I live alone.
我來洛杉磯沒幾周
I've only been in L.A. a couple weeks.
我認識的男人只有你和弗蘭克
The only men in my life are you and Frank.
好吧  那弗蘭克的聯系方式是...
Oh, all right. How do I get a hold of Frank?
他是頭豬[壞男人]
He's a pig.
他是豬  你是霍爾[雞]
He's a pig, you're a Hore.
沒人會說三道四的
No one's judging.
不  它是我的寵物豬
No, he's my pet pig.
我的小豬腸
My little frankfurter.
一只豬啊
A pig.
他睡在毛毯里嗎
Does he sleep in a blanket?
是啊  他每次都會把毛毯頂起來
Yeah, he totally hogs the covers.
"頂"起來  說得好
Hogs. Good one.
當我沒說
Never mind.
那藥物呢
Uh, what about medications?
超愛的
Love 'em.
不是  我是問"現在有在服用其他藥物"
No, I-I think they mean "Are you taking any now?"
我相信啊  我有在吃治療抑郁癥的藥
Oh, let's see, there's plaxitril for my depression,
治療焦慮癥的藥
zaxaprin for my anxiety,
治療失眠的藥
dilapamin for my insomnia,
還有治療間歇性失控行為的藥
and clodex for my occasional bouts of rage.
誰都不喜歡憤怒的霍爾[妓女]
No one likes an angry Hore.
你怎么不早說咱們來的是同志酒吧
Why didn't you tell me we were going to a gay bar?
我要是早告訴你  你肯定不來了
'Cause if I told you, you wouldn't have come.
我肯定會來  而且會穿得更好看點
Yes, I would. I just would've dressed better.
不過先說清楚
And just to be clear,
你知道我不是同性戀吧
you do know I'm not gay, right?
我覺得你不是同性戀啊
I don't think you're gay.
雖然我也認識很多行為爺們
I-I mean, do I know guys that act less gay
但是會跟男人做愛的男人
that have sex with other guys? Sure.
不過我知道你是直男
But I know you're straight.
那你帶我來干什么
So, why bring me here?
你掃一眼這里
Look around this room.
-看到那些女人了嗎  -看到了
- See all the women here? - Yeah.
有些女人是同性戀  她們是我的
Well, some of them are gay. Those are mine.
剩下的就是異性戀
The rest are straight.
當然  其中也有一些是我的
Some of those are mine, too.
最后落單的那些女人
And everyone who's left
在打烊的時候就會喝得爛醉如泥  欲火焚身
is gonna be drunk and horny by the end of the night
然后會尋找那些不覺得陰道很"不好吃"的人
and looking for someone who doesn't think vaginas are yucky.
原來你是在說我
Oh, oh, you mean me.
好棒哦
Yay.
我是說  不錯
I mean, yay.
小心點
Okay, be careful.
小心腿
Watch your leg.
-你身上好香  -謝謝
- You smell so good. - Thank you.
讓我來嘗嘗你的味道
Let's see how you taste.
行了  行了
Okay. All right.
看來止痛藥有效果了
I see the painkillers have kicked in.
當然有效果
Oh, they sure did.
現在  你可以對我做任何事
Right now, you could do anything to me
而且我都不會記得哦
and I wouldn't remember.
剛我拋媚眼了嗎  我想拋來著
Did I wink? 'Cause I was trying to wink.
行了  你先去沙發上坐會吧
Okay, let's-let's get you on the couch, huh?
-那你在我身上"做"會吧  -好吧
- Hey, let's get you on Nadine. - Oh, okay.
行了  先  先歇一會吧
All right, fine. Let's... just rest.
真的很感謝你照顧我
Thank you so much for taking care of me.
畢竟  你斷了一條腿
Well, you have a broken leg.
而且沒有家人  沒有朋友
You don't have any family or friends
而且你住在四樓  還沒有電梯
and you live on the fourth floor of a building with no elevator.
我總不能把你扔在大街上吧
So, I couldn't just leave you on the street.
可以嗎
Could I?
-你好帥哦  -我知道
- You're handsome. - Yeah.
你...在流口水
You're... drooling.
我去給你拿點吃的
I'm gonna get you some food.
好吧  不過我飲食有忌口
All right, but I have certain dietary constrictions.
我不吃小麥  不吃乳制品  也不吃帶臉的
I don't eat wheat, dairy, or anything with a face.
不過
Although...
我可以為了你破戒
I would make an exception for you.
所以你跟侄女一起來的嗎
So, you're here with your niece?
是啊  她最近剛出柜
Uh, yeah, she just recently came out of the closet
而且她非常害羞
and she's painfully shy.
這才叫母乳喂養[吮吸胸部]
Now, that's what I call breast-feeding.
她還在慢慢適應的過程中
She's, uh, still trying to find her gay legs.
是嗎  所幸她叔叔已經完全適應了
Ah. Well, she's lucky she has an uncle who's found his.
不  我是直男
No, I'm straight.
為什么大家都覺得我是同性戀
Why does everybody think I'm gay?
哎喲  這個好酸哦
Oh, that is way too tart.
寶拉
Um, so, Paula,
你是做什么的
what do you do?
我是個投資銀行家
I'm an investment banker.
那你能不能回答我一個一直想問的問題
Oh, okay, maybe you can answer a question I've always had.
提前取款[抽出]有什么后果嗎
What's the penalty for early withdrawal?
這要看情況
Well, uh, that depends.
你的"存款"有多大
How big is your deposit?
利息[性趣]多"起來"了
Oh, interest is rising.
其實呢  在"里面"存得越久
You know, the longer you keep it in,
"收益"就會越多
the bigger your reward.
可是有時  市場會"疲軟倒下"
Sometimes, the market collapses
而你卻也無力改變
and there's nothing you can do about it.
等一下  這段對話到底是性暗示
Uh, wait. Are-are we doing sexual innuendo
還是你在咨詢我免費的理財建議
or are you asking for free financial advice?
不能兩者皆是嗎
Why can't it be both?
其實  如果你有興趣的話
You know, if you're interested,
我在馬里布海灘有棟別墅
I've got a Malibu beach house.
如果你有興趣的話  我沒什么道德底線
Well, if you're interested, I've got very loose morals.
好棒哦
Yay.
應該是  不錯
I mean, yay.
剛剛好爽哦
That was amazing.
你不喜歡嗎  我可以做得更好的
Wait, it wasn't? 'Cause I can do better.
不  你做得很好
No, you were great.
謝天謝地  因為剛才就做到最好了
Oh, thank God, 'cause I can't do better.
不過有件事在上床前
But there is something I probably should've told you
我就應該告訴你的
before we slept together.
是有老公了  還是有性病
Oh, God, husband or herpes?
有個男人  他叫保羅
Well, there was another guy. Paul.
保羅  寶拉  肯定不容易分清
Paul. Paula. That must have been confusing...
是啊
Very, yeah. Um...
其實  在40歲以前
You see, for the first 40 years of my life,
我是一個叫保羅的男人
I was a man named Paul.
你看起來不像...40歲
You don't look... 40.
這么說  你以前也是個男人
So, so, you were a guy?
也有喉結和胡子嗎
With, you know, an Adam's apple and facial hair,
還有下面那整套裝備嗎
and the whole kit and kaboodle?
是的  那整套裝備我都有
Yep, I had a kit and two kaboodles.
那你怎么變成這樣了
So, so, how did you get that?
我是說  你用找人捐贈器官嗎
I mean, did you have to get a donor?
拿駕照要填以后捐不捐器官的時候
'Cause I've never seen that box
我沒見過有捐"那部分"的選項啊
to check on a driver's license.
事實上  是我把器官捐給別人了
Actually, uh, I-I... I donated my own organ.
我要做的就是切掉雞雞  懂嗎
You see, what they do, they take your penis, all right?
對準中央  一刀切下
They slice it right down the middle...
好吧  我蛋蛋具體經歷了什么
Okay, I'll-I'll spare you the details
就不給你講那么詳細了
on what happened to my balls.
我倒清楚我蛋蛋怎么了
Well, I know what just happened to mine.
我知道應該早點告訴你的
Look, I-I know I should have told you earlier.
我只是不想把你嚇跑  我真的喜歡你
I just didn't want to scare you away. I really like you.
我也喜歡你  我們有很多相似之處
Oh, and I like you. I mean, we have a lot in common.
而且比我知道的還"多"
Clearly more than I realized.
或許我該離開
Maybe it's best if I go.
不  不  不要走
Oh, no, no, don't do.
你確定嗎
You sure?
對啊  別走  我喜歡你
Yeah, yeah, no, I like you.
我只是在盡力消化這件事
I'm just, I'm trying to process this whole thing.
我是說  比如
I mean, for instance,
你的雞雞不會再長回來了  對吧
there's no chance it'll grow back, right?
就像蜥蜴的尾巴那樣嗎
What, like-like a salamander's tail?
不會
No. Uh-uh.
你不會有一天打噴嚏用力過猛
So one day you're not gonna, you know, sneeze real hard
突然把雞雞噴出來吧
and suddenly I'm dating a dude?
艾倫  我跟你以前的女人沒有區別
Alan, I am as much a woman as you've ever dated.
但是如果你不能接受我的過去  那...
But if you're not okay with this, it's...
不  不  算了
No, no, no, you know what?
我不會讓一點小事影響我們的關系
I am not going to let one little thing come between us.
我那"事"可不算小
Oh, it wasn't little.
寶拉  算是兩性關系建議吧
Okay, uh, Paula, bit of, uh, relationship advice?
沒有一個男人希望聽到
Uh, no guy likes to hear
女朋友的雞雞比他大
that his girlfriend had a bigger penis than he does.
你說得對
You're right.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
保重身體[德語]
Gesundheit.
-早安  -早安
-Morning. -Morning.
媽的  培根沒了
Oh great, we're out of bacon.
裸體超模也沒了
We're out of naked Heidi Klum.
靠
Damn.
這是弗蘭克  是我女伴納丁養的寵物
That's Frank. He belongs to my date Nadine.
艾倫跟我說了
Alan told me about her.
就是那個被你帶去急診室的模特
That's the model you took to the emergency room.
而且是兩次  她稱之為我們的"定情地"
Twice. She calls it our "special place."
這是我人生中最糟糕的一次約會
It's the worst date of my life.
你撐爛了她的嘴嗎
Is her mouth broken?
不是
No.
那問題是什么
So what's the problem?
問題在于  我們不來電
The problem is, we have no connection.
如果不愛一個女人的心靈
How can I be attracted to a woman's body
又怎能愛上她的身體呢
if I'm not attracted to her mind?
聽起來有點像同性戀  不過也沒什么
Sounds kind of gay, but all right.
早啊  沃頓
Hey, Walden.
珍妮
Jenny.
廢柴[艾倫]
Zippy.
友情提示  有個女孩睡在沙發上
Just a heads-up, there's a girl asleep on the couch.
放心老板  我知道怎么做
Don't worry, I know the drill, boss.
給她500塊  搜她身上有沒有偷銀具
Give her 500 bucks, pat her down for silverware
然后丟進計程車
and throw her in a taxi.
什么
What?
抱歉  突然想到了查理
Sorry. Charlie flashback.
早上好
Morning.
這是一頭豬啊
That's a pig.
這是一只吸血蟲啊
Whoa! That's a leech.
說來話長  離譜的一晚
Long story, crazy night.
不管有沒有豬  你都沒我離譜
Pig or no pig, not as crazy as mine.
100塊賭我比你離譜
100 bucks says mine beats yours.
我跟一個曾經是男人的女人上床了
I had sex with a woman who used to be a man.
勝負見分曉啦
And we have a winner.
真的嗎
What, really?
我不相信你會...
I can't believe that you would...
不過轉念一想  也不出奇
Well, ah, then again, it's you.
隨你怎么說
Hey, hey, say what you want,
但她真的很懂怎么侍候男人
but she really knows her way around a man.
就像跟優秀的西藏向導一起爬珠峰
It's like climbing Mount Everest with a really good Sherpa.
是啊  但你不和西藏向導上床啊
Yeah, but you don't shtup the Sherpa.
怎么變性啊  那玩意去哪兒了呢
How did it work? Like, where did it... go?
很容易的  只需
Oh, that's easy. See, what they do is,
對準中央  一刀切下
they slice the penis down the middle...
沃頓
Walden?
我能不能洗個澡呢
Is there somewhere I can take a bath?
當然  在樓上  我來幫你
Oh, yeah, upstairs. Here, I'll help you.
不
No.
如果我什么事都靠你
I will never get out of here
就永遠不能離開這里
if I don't start to do things on my own.
除非你不想讓我離開
Unless you don't want me to leave.
樓上  左手邊
Top of the stairs, on the left.
這個女孩傷得太重了
That girl is really messed up.
我那位唯一讓我不爽的
The only thing wrong with mine
就是她偶爾新長出的胡須
is the occasional five o'clock shadow.
我要說  艾倫
You know, I've got to say, Alan,
你和一個術后變性人約會
you going out with a post-op transgendered person
而心中沒有任何偏見
without any judgment--
我覺得很贊
very enlightened.
謝謝
Oh, thank you.
你該見識見識她的咪咪
And you should see her boobs.
一個叫霍爾[妓女]的打來電話
You're getting a call from a "Hore?"
喂  納丁
Hi, Nadine.
你把它卡到哪里了
You got... you got it stuck where?
不要動  我馬上過去
Don't move, I'll be right there.
納丁的護靴卡到樓梯扶欄里了
Nadine got her boot caught in the banister.
失陪了
Excuse me.
不用了  我搞定了
Never mind, I got it.
給個500塊加計程車費  他早脫身了
500 bucks and cab fare, and he'd be out of this.
真不敢相信我們這么容易就選定電影了
I can't believe how easily we agreed on a movie.
就是啊  男人和女人總是很難達成一致
I know, men and women aren't usually on the same page.
就是這里
Oh, oh, here it is.
三號廳  《茱麗婭·羅伯茨我愛你》
Uh, theater three, Julia Roberts in Hashtag: I Love You.
我去買汽水  你要不要來點什么
Listen, I'm gonna get a soda. Do you want something?
當然  我看看我想吃什么
Oh, sure. Uh, oh, let me see what I'm in the mood for.
想分著吃熱狗嗎[剪開雞雞]
Oh, uh, want to split a hot dog?
太對不起了
Oh, I am so sorry.
沒事
It's fine.
你好  麻煩給我兩杯健怡可樂
Hi. Uh, can we have two Diet Cokes
一份熱狗
and a hot dog, please?
不用了  我來
Don't worry, I got it.
好吧  但我習慣了男人付錢
Okay, but I'm used to paying.
這真是太奇怪了
This is... this is so weird.
對不起  這是保羅的舊習慣
Sorry, just, you know, old habits from when I was Paul.
我希望你沒有意見
I-I hope you're okay with that.
我想很明顯我很樂意
I think it's pretty clear that I'm willing
適應這段關系
to work around things in this relationship.
太感謝了
Well, I appreciate it,
因為我和你在一起很開心
because I'm having a great time with you.
我也是
Oh, well, so am I.
但往后  你得學會
Uh, but going forward, you're gonna have to learn
適應我的男子氣概  接受這個事實
to embrace my masculinity and, you know, accept the fact
我才是  謝謝
that I'm the-- thank you--
這段關系里的男性角色
man in this relationship.
這里好冷
Oh, it's chilly in here.
給  外套給你
Oh, here. Take my jacket.
好溫暖哦
Oh. Cozy.
是誰
Who's there?
是我  小傻瓜
It's just me, silly.
你還好嗎
Is everything all right?
你把我照顧得這么好
You've taken such good care of me,
我想是時候
I thought it was time for me
我來好好"照顧"你
to take good care of you.
沒這個必要
Oh, that's not necessary.
為什么
Why not?
我們可以扮醫生
We could play doctor.
你看醫生還沒看夠嗎
Haven't you seen enough doctors?
好吧  我們扮演帕特和瓦娜
Okay, we could play Pat and Vanna.
線索是  人們脫光了做的事
The clue is "Things people do naked."
納丁  別這樣
Okay, Nadine, just stop.
有什么不對
What's wrong?
我不會和你上床的
We're not gonna sleep together.
你是說
Are you saying
你不想要這個尤物嗎
that you don't want any of this?
不想  一百萬個不情愿
"N," And I'd like to buy five O's.
我們之間不來電
Look, we-we just don't click.
你居然這樣誤導我
I can't believe you led me on.
哪有  我是讓你進門  幫助你
Led you on? I let you in. I was trying to help you.
我看起來需要你的幫助嗎
Do I look like I need your help?
喂  我沒做什么
Yeah? No, I'm not doing anything.
不是吧
Seriously?
就是啊  我應該出個聲
I know, I know. I should say something.
不  算了
No, no, it's fine.
我看完電影后過去
I'll come over after the movie.
他現在就該走
He should go now.
你說什么
What's that?
無視他就行  你搭理他
Just ignore him. People can only make you angry
只會讓你生氣
with your permission.
好  但如果他再開口  我就去找引座員
Right. But if he opens his mouth again, I will get the usher.
我的影評就是
I got my review.
#一部爛片
Hashtag piece of crap.
好吧  受夠了
All right, you know what? That's it.
慢著  別這樣  讓我來
Oh, wait, oh, no, no, no, Let me do this.
艾倫  你不用這么做
Alan, Alan, you don't have to do this.
我是男人
Yes, I do. I'm the man
這是男人做的事  幫我拿著果膠軟糖
and this is what a man does. Now, hold my Jujubes.
-不好意思  先生  -什么事
- Uh, excuse me, sir? - What?
大家在看電影呢
Um, uh, we're all trying to watch the movie
我不知道你是否記得
and I don't know if you remember what the, uh,
卡通爆米花桶提醒過
the little cartoon popcorn bucket said,
沉默是金
but "Silence is golden."
是嗎  你想怎樣
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do about it?
我已經做了
Uh, well, I just did it
但沒啥成效  所以...
and it didn't seem very effective, so...
回去坐下吧
Go sit down.
知道嗎  不如你坐下吧
Okay, you know what? Why don't you sit down?
搞什么  搞什么
What the... What...
對不起
I'm sorry.
不用道歉
Don't apologize.
寶拉  我愛你
Paula? Hashtag I love you.
我還以為這段關系能夠有結果[去哪里]
I thought this relationship was going somewhere.
你說真的嗎  這段關系唯一去的地方
Okay, seriously? The only place this relationship is going
就是急診室
is the emergency room.
我以為咱們之間是特別的
I thought this was something special.
我以為我會成為納丁·霍爾施密特[馬屎]夫人
I thought I was going to be Mrs. Nadine Hore-Schmidt.
這也太瘋狂了
Okay, this is crazy.
如果你沒有從我家陽臺上掉下去
I mean, we wouldn't have gotten past the first date
我們第一次約會早不了了之了
if you hadn't fallen off my deck.
沒錯
That's right.
我的確從你家陽臺上掉下去了
I did fall off your deck.
我會向我的律師提到這點的
I'll be sure to mention that to my lawyer.
你的律師
Your lawyer?
沒錯
You heard me.
也許你在巴士車身上見過他的照片
Perhaps you've seen his picture on the side of the bus?
成為頂級意外事故律師
You don't get to be the numero uno accidente lawyer
可不是靠意外的
by accident.
走吧  弗蘭克
Come on, Frank.
你多保重  弗蘭克
Take care of yourself, Frank.
出什么事了
What's going on?
納丁準備告我
Oh, Nadine is going to sue me
因為我不愿意和她上床
because I won't sleep with her.
還有這種事啊
Oh, that's a thing?
別告訴艾倫
Don't tell Alan.
不可能吧
Oh, that can't be.
你好  納丁
Hi, Nadine.
我馬上過去
I'll be right there.
納丁被巴士撞了
Nadine got hit by a bus.
又要回到我和她的定情地了
Back to our special place.
你想看什么
What do you want to watch?
我知道有人想再看一遍《小豬寶貝》
I know someone wants to watch Babe again.